Sir, we have been focusing on Reliance for many days continuously.
What is the update on that now
?
Absolutely, there has been a rise in Reliance for the second consecutive day.  Just
imagine, even in a bad market,
higher highs were made and lower lows were also made.  This
means that there are full signs of volatility
in Reliance, it is still trying to move up and down.  Let's
see what
happens.  The 2-month high in intraday
is 1451 but Reliance closed
at 1483 above the 100 DMA of 1466, so the
closing was good.  Even though it
went below 100 DMA in intraday, the closing was good.
Reliance
is 8% below the life high of 1611 that it had made on January 5 and
you will remember that we had also said in the insight that it
tried to cross the level of 1600 twice last year but could not cross it and the same thing happened for the
third time also.  A
big correction seems to be coming from there.  There was a
correction of 8% in three-four days.  HDFC Bank
My goodness what happened to him?  From the day the
quarterly update was given, it has been
very weak since then, so weak on the sixth day
and on the fifth day it is making lower high lower low.
Yesterday it made a 9-month low of 929, that is the
magic of Bank Nifty.
Standing strong despite that.  After 9 months, HDFC Bank
closed at 939 the day before yesterday, very close to the make or break level of 940 or the biggest support level.  We're going to be
around 937 on I mean Friday and tomorrow.  It's
closing right there.
If it stays below it and closes in a proper
manner from below, suppose if it gives a closing of 92530,
yes
it will give a new breakdown on the 9-month low.
Similarly, on intraday closing basis
also, if a 9-month low is made at 940, it has happened
many times where it
reached 940 at least four times, it recovers and comes
back up in the range of 980000. This
time for the first time, there is a fear that it is falling and
not increasing.
Although, since we did that research on 940, it has been
four days since then, 9 is weak but it is
not going below ₹940 properly.
Now for ₹23, can you say that?  There
is not much difference between ₹940 and 937.  So let's see,
HDFC Bank is at the make and break level,
meanwhile ICICI Bank made lower high lower low for the second consecutive day.
Although it
also closed in the green mark at 1413, this is a good
thing.  ICICI Bank was overbought on January 8.
When its RSI reached 72.
Hi, he made it for Rs 1442, then we said that
we will not buy it now.   The
first thing is to sell and keep a stop loss.
Neha ji, from the overbought level, it
made a local of 1391 from 1442, it gave a fall of 3.5%
in two days, 3.5% in two-three sessions
and let me tell you from where this study came.  This
happened twice in 2025.  ICICI
Bank's RSI reached 68 and
from there it started falling sharply.  The first one happened on July 20, 2025, when the
RSI closed at 68 and
ICICI Bank fell by 5% in three weeks. The second time it happened on October 17,
2025, when the RSI closed at 1436
and fell by 8% in two weeks. This time again a
high of 1442 has been made, almost around the same range, and
in just two days, it has lost 3.5%. So,
ICICI Bank's clear cut is also in front of you.